<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Coby Randal on Sons of God Ministries International</title>
    <link>sogmi.org/authors/coby-randal/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Coby Randal on Sons of God Ministries International</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2014 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="sogmi.org/authors/coby-randal/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
        <title>Prophecy for 2014</title>
        
            <dc:creator>Coby Randal</dc:creator>
        
        <link>sogmi.org/articles/prophecy-for-2014/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>sogmi.org/articles/prophecy-for-2014/</guid>
        
            <media:content url="//images.contentful.com/vfgh62eq5a4k/4AOoedF1KEMmMU2SuOSKUo/1ab9ef10e297827ef1f36628355f2646/good-free-photos-561-unsplash.jpg?w=800" medium="image/jpg"/>
        
        <description>The following is an excerpt from the December 31, 2013 Prophetic Conference:
Prophecy for 2014  We are entering a new season, a season like no other. Great harvest of souls in every area of our lives. Harvest for the Body of Christ will be exponential and in accelerated pace/time. The revival in United States as a country will start in the political arena, then in the financial, educational arena.</description>
        <category>articles</category>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>New Radio Program - The Prophetic Voice of Our Time</title>
        
            <dc:creator>Coby Randal</dc:creator>
        
        <link>sogmi.org/articles/new-radio-program-the-prophetic-voice-of-our-time/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>sogmi.org/articles/new-radio-program-the-prophetic-voice-of-our-time/</guid>
        
            <media:content url="//images.contentful.com/vfgh62eq5a4k/4ZnFL8TtW0i6EoiUCI4MYE/3d494775182c64d906e1bef4e8be2e30/condenser-mic-compressor.jpg?w=800" medium="image/jpg"/>
        
        <description>We are excited to announce Pastor Cris is back on KSLR!
A Prophet&amp;rsquo;s Reward - Part 1 Find out what the word says about the office of a prophet. http://www.sogmi.org/podcasts/TPVOT/TPVOT_E010_12_10_13_A_Prophets_Reward_Part1.mp3
A Prophet&amp;rsquo;s Reward - Part 2 Continued Find out what the word says about the office of a prophet. http://www.sogmi.org/podcasts/TPVOT/TPVOT_E011_12_10_14_A_Prophets_Reward_Part2.mp3
Tune into Radio Station 630 KSLR-AM (or Listen Live @ www.kslr.com), or checkout previous episodes on our podcasts page. KSLR will be airing our first broadcast of The Prophetic Voice Of Our Time at 6:30 p.</description>
        <category>articles</category>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Prophecy to the Church</title>
        
            <dc:creator>Coby Randal</dc:creator>
        
        <link>sogmi.org/articles/prophecy-to-the-church/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Nov 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>sogmi.org/articles/prophecy-to-the-church/</guid>
        
            <media:content url="//images.contentful.com/vfgh62eq5a4k/5KH3rRY5FuC4iaYoykeUEs/0c30b64b0c4a40c192d2fc121fc6153a/ben-white-292680-unsplash__1_.jpg?w=800" medium="image/jpg"/>
        
        <description>The following is a prophecy released back in 2010
We are entering a time when personal prophecy will become more and more rare. Continuing to hear the testimony of Jesus Christ, the prophetic mantle will address the Body increasingly on a corporate level instead of an individual level. Yes, remember the personal prophetic words that were released to you, but more important than that is the need for you to follow your prophetic instructions, concerning the Body of Christ and the Nations, to the letter.</description>
        <category>articles</category>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Revival is Here</title>
        
            <dc:creator>Coby Randal</dc:creator>
        
        <link>sogmi.org/articles/revival-is-here/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>sogmi.org/articles/revival-is-here/</guid>
        
        <description>The fruits and signs that revival has come include:
True repentance brought on by the Holy Spirit; Jesus becomes not just Savior, but Lord over every area. Focus on the presence of God, knowing Him and His word. Falling in love with Jesus; not getting drunk on visions or gifts. A grateful heart of worship; God multiplies our faith by His word and faith works by love. We are delivered from the tree of the knowledge of good and evil, not striving about fear or emotions, but looking steadfastly upon Jesus, living by faith in Him that we may please God by Him in us.</description>
        <category>articles</category>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Prophecy From July 12, 2009</title>
        
            <dc:creator>Coby Randal</dc:creator>
        
        <link>sogmi.org/articles/prophecy-from-july-12-2009/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jul 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>sogmi.org/articles/prophecy-from-july-12-2009/</guid>
        
        <description>This is an excerpt of the July 12, 2009 prophecy given by the Lord through Pastor Cris.
The same thing that I did in the Philippines, with accreditation of signs and wonders in the realm of finances, saith the Lord, I will do now, if you are going to confer with Me, if you are going to put Me first, and if you are going to obey what you have learned and your instructions, saith the Lord, it will manifest starting this year.</description>
        <category>articles</category>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>