<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Cristina Sosso on Sons of God Ministries International</title>
    <link>/authors/cristina-sosso/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Cristina Sosso on Sons of God Ministries International</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="/authors/cristina-sosso/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
        <title>The Importance of Prophecy Today</title>
        
            <dc:creator>Cristina Sosso</dc:creator>
        
        <link>/articles/the-importance-of-prophecy-today/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>/articles/the-importance-of-prophecy-today/</guid>
        
            <media:content url="//images.contentful.com/vfgh62eq5a4k/1GuemKD6EMYKcgq6IsoMuG/8a8b51eeccccad30e34c6d12bc138ca6/jeremy-bishop-184462-unsplash.jpg?w=800" medium="image/jpg"/>
        
        <description>The Big Oxmox advised her not to do so, because there were thousands of bad Commas, wild Question Marks and devious Semikoli, but the Little Blind Text didn’t listen. She packed her seven versalia, put her initial into the belt and made herself on the way. When she reached the first hills of the Italic Mountains, she had a last view back on the skyline of her hometown Bookmarksgrove, the headline of Alphabet Village and the subline of her own road, the Line Lane.</description>
        <category>articles</category>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>A Warning to the False Prophets of Our Day</title>
        
            <dc:creator>Cristina Sosso</dc:creator>
        
        <link>/articles/warning-to-the-false-prophets-of-our-day/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>/articles/warning-to-the-false-prophets-of-our-day/</guid>
        
            <media:content url="//images.contentful.com/vfgh62eq5a4k/3Pcb2gom2sqwYAM0YcY4GA/80996a9f95185bf0498e86c27fc09428/wrong-way-sign-export-compressor.jpg?w=800" medium="image/jpg"/>
        
        <description>Brothers and sisters in Christ, these are exciting and glorious times. It is time for great expectations and also greater work. The United States of America is not going down! She is going up! For those “doom and gloom” prophets who prophesy against the United States and speak of its demise, they better not hold their breath, because it is not going to happen in this generation, not while you and I are still here!</description>
        <category>articles</category>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>What a Great Time to be Alive</title>
        
            <dc:creator>Cristina Sosso</dc:creator>
        
        <link>/articles/what-a-great-time-to-be-alive/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>/articles/what-a-great-time-to-be-alive/</guid>
        
            <media:content url="//images.contentful.com/vfgh62eq5a4k/4nw4mfMDOUUgUs4mOA08My/ac407c2b321fffd8b6052662550eb959/kristina-wagner-357533-unsplash__1_.jpg?w=800" medium="image/jpg"/>
        
        <description>I cannot put into words the awesome wonders of our Lord Jesus Christ! All I can say is that it is great to be alive (in Christ). Right before our eyes, we see the transformation of our nation and this is just the beginning! What’s even more exciting than this is the fact the Lord always shares His plans, His thoughts, and His heart with the Body of Christ if we have ears to hear and eyes to see!</description>
        <category>articles</category>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>A Word About the Transfer of Wealth</title>
        
            <dc:creator>Cristina Sosso</dc:creator>
        
        <link>/articles/a-word-about-the-transfer-of-wealth/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>/articles/a-word-about-the-transfer-of-wealth/</guid>
        
            <media:content url="//images.contentful.com/vfgh62eq5a4k/1Konxep5rK8Y6egiImGAcG/d2d2b495e23632ab6c7cb5044d81c794/freddie-collins-309833-unsplash__1_.jpg?w=800" medium="image/jpg"/>
        
        <description>In 1991, I was caught in a dream-like vision. In this encounter with God, He handed me a formula on how to find His kingdom. It was a series of very detailed instructions He expected me to follow. He told me that He would be sending laborers who would follow my lead, knowing fully well that they would find the kingdom. These people were matured and did not desire material things.</description>
        <category>articles</category>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>I Am Restoring the Judges as in the Days of Old</title>
        
            <dc:creator>Cristina Sosso</dc:creator>
        
        <link>/articles/i-am-restoring-the-judges-as-in-the-days-of-old/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 22 Aug 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>/articles/i-am-restoring-the-judges-as-in-the-days-of-old/</guid>
        
            <media:content url="//images.contentful.com/vfgh62eq5a4k/6o5dw9ihQAcmM0C2mAkSu0/b1d6f13daa41c774c03045f97f7395aa/Sans_C3_B3n_matando_al_le_C3_B3n_-_Pedro_Pablo_Rubens.jpg?w=800" medium="image/jpg"/>
        
        <description>The following is a prophecy from August 22nd 2010.
Thus saith the Lord of hosts, “As I am restoring the judges as in the days of old, as I am a faithful God, not only for this nation, but for the nations of the Earth to bring forth the nations to the proper places of alignment and timing including the nation of Israel. This is your beckoning. This is your calling.</description>
        <category>articles</category>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>