<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Articles on Sons of God Ministries International</title>
    <link>sogmi.org/articles/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Articles on Sons of God Ministries International</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="sogmi.org/articles/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
        <title>The Importance of Prophecy Today</title>
        
            <dc:creator>Cristina Sosso</dc:creator>
        
        <link>sogmi.org/articles/the-importance-of-prophecy-today/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>sogmi.org/articles/the-importance-of-prophecy-today/</guid>
        
            <media:content url="//images.contentful.com/vfgh62eq5a4k/1GuemKD6EMYKcgq6IsoMuG/8a8b51eeccccad30e34c6d12bc138ca6/jeremy-bishop-184462-unsplash.jpg?w=800" medium="image/jpg"/>
        
        <description>The Big Oxmox advised her not to do so, because there were thousands of bad Commas, wild Question Marks and devious Semikoli, but the Little Blind Text didn’t listen. She packed her seven versalia, put her initial into the belt and made herself on the way. When she reached the first hills of the Italic Mountains, she had a last view back on the skyline of her hometown Bookmarksgrove, the headline of Alphabet Village and the subline of her own road, the Line Lane.</description>
        <category>articles</category>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>God is Bringing About the Transfer of Wealth</title>
        
            <dc:creator>Joshua Sosso</dc:creator>
        
        <link>sogmi.org/articles/god-is-bringing-about-the-transfer-of-wealth/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>sogmi.org/articles/god-is-bringing-about-the-transfer-of-wealth/</guid>
        
            <media:content url="//images.contentful.com/vfgh62eq5a4k/1fzeTsLoaiccqAKQuY6mgs/df8fe77f5c0f3acb1cf8651879c4209e/olu-eletu-38649-unsplash__1_.jpg?w=800" medium="image/jpg"/>
        
        <description>A wonderful serenity has taken possession of my entire soul, like these sweet mornings of spring which I enjoy with my whole heart. I am alone, and feel the charm of existence in this spot, which was created for the bliss of souls like mine. I am so happy, my dear friend, so absorbed in the exquisite sense of mere tranquil existence, that I neglect my talents.
 I should be incapable of drawing a single stroke at the present moment; and yet I feel that I never was a greater artist than now.</description>
        <category>articles</category>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>6 Characteristics Christians Should Look for in Political Leaders</title>
        
            <dc:creator>Mike Sosso</dc:creator>
        
        <link>sogmi.org/articles/godsguidelineforelections/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>sogmi.org/articles/godsguidelineforelections/</guid>
        
            <media:content url="//images.contentful.com/vfgh62eq5a4k/5UvagPHWDK62ws6Wy808ce/bf8e90962701acda5f785ee00663cefd/1456519101974?w=800" medium="image/jpg"/>
        
        <description>Eight years ago, the Lord spoke to us prophetically saying “If My people will unite, this nation can have and will have the most righteous leaders and government she has ever had since its inception, and even greater.” You may ask, “Is that possible?” but nothing is impossible with God! However for this to happen, we have to unite, and the only way we will ever unite politically, is if we unite on the truth and principles found in God’s Word.</description>
        <category>articles</category>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Prophecy for 2014</title>
        
            <dc:creator>Coby Randal</dc:creator>
        
        <link>sogmi.org/articles/prophecy-for-2014/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>sogmi.org/articles/prophecy-for-2014/</guid>
        
            <media:content url="//images.contentful.com/vfgh62eq5a4k/4AOoedF1KEMmMU2SuOSKUo/1ab9ef10e297827ef1f36628355f2646/good-free-photos-561-unsplash.jpg?w=800" medium="image/jpg"/>
        
        <description>The following is an excerpt from the December 31, 2013 Prophetic Conference:
Prophecy for 2014  We are entering a new season, a season like no other. Great harvest of souls in every area of our lives. Harvest for the Body of Christ will be exponential and in accelerated pace/time. The revival in United States as a country will start in the political arena, then in the financial, educational arena.</description>
        <category>articles</category>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>URGENT MESSAGE: God&#39;s Guidelines For Choosing Our Nations Leaders</title>
        
            <dc:creator>Mike Sosso</dc:creator>
        
        <link>sogmi.org/articles/urgent-message-gods-guidelines-for-choosing-our-nations-leaders/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>sogmi.org/articles/urgent-message-gods-guidelines-for-choosing-our-nations-leaders/</guid>
        
            <media:content url="//images.contentful.com/vfgh62eq5a4k/zRSQiJ1LQyICyI8GM6aGa/f7809061e3f5f65fcc5569f234e75f72/jomar-271602-unsplash-compressor.jpg?w=800" medium="image/jpg"/>
        
        <description>Dear Partners and Friends,
Four years ago, the Lord spoke prophetically and said; “If My people will unite, this nation can have the most righteous leaders and government she has ever had since its inception, and even greater.” You may say, is that possible? Is anything impossible for God? No! But for this to happen, we must meet the criteria and unite, and the only way we can unite politically, is to unite around truth found in God’s Word.</description>
        <category>articles</category>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>URGENT MESSAGE: God&#39;s Guidelines For Choosing Our Nations Leaders</title>
        
            <dc:creator>Mike Sosso</dc:creator>
        
        <link>sogmi.org/articles/urgent-message-gods-guidelines-for-choosing-our-nations-leaders/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>sogmi.org/articles/urgent-message-gods-guidelines-for-choosing-our-nations-leaders/</guid>
        
            <media:content url="//images.contentful.com/vfgh62eq5a4k/zRSQiJ1LQyICyI8GM6aGa/f7809061e3f5f65fcc5569f234e75f72/jomar-271602-unsplash-compressor.jpg?w=800" medium="image/jpg"/>
        
        <description>Dear Partners and Friends,
Four years ago, the Lord spoke prophetically and said; “If My people will unite, this nation can have the most righteous leaders and government she has ever had since its inception, and even greater.” You may say, is that possible? Is anything impossible for God? No! But for this to happen, we must meet the criteria and unite, and the only way we can unite politically, is to unite around truth found in God’s Word.</description>
        <category>articles</category>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>New Radio Program - The Prophetic Voice of Our Time</title>
        
            <dc:creator>Coby Randal</dc:creator>
        
        <link>sogmi.org/articles/new-radio-program-the-prophetic-voice-of-our-time/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>sogmi.org/articles/new-radio-program-the-prophetic-voice-of-our-time/</guid>
        
            <media:content url="//images.contentful.com/vfgh62eq5a4k/4ZnFL8TtW0i6EoiUCI4MYE/3d494775182c64d906e1bef4e8be2e30/condenser-mic-compressor.jpg?w=800" medium="image/jpg"/>
        
        <description>We are excited to announce Pastor Cris is back on KSLR!
A Prophet&amp;rsquo;s Reward - Part 1 Find out what the word says about the office of a prophet. http://www.sogmi.org/podcasts/TPVOT/TPVOT_E010_12_10_13_A_Prophets_Reward_Part1.mp3
A Prophet&amp;rsquo;s Reward - Part 2 Continued Find out what the word says about the office of a prophet. http://www.sogmi.org/podcasts/TPVOT/TPVOT_E011_12_10_14_A_Prophets_Reward_Part2.mp3
Tune into Radio Station 630 KSLR-AM (or Listen Live @ www.kslr.com), or checkout previous episodes on our podcasts page. KSLR will be airing our first broadcast of The Prophetic Voice Of Our Time at 6:30 p.</description>
        <category>articles</category>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>A Warning to the False Prophets of Our Day</title>
        
            <dc:creator>Cristina Sosso</dc:creator>
        
        <link>sogmi.org/articles/warning-to-the-false-prophets-of-our-day/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>sogmi.org/articles/warning-to-the-false-prophets-of-our-day/</guid>
        
            <media:content url="//images.contentful.com/vfgh62eq5a4k/3Pcb2gom2sqwYAM0YcY4GA/80996a9f95185bf0498e86c27fc09428/wrong-way-sign-export-compressor.jpg?w=800" medium="image/jpg"/>
        
        <description>Brothers and sisters in Christ, these are exciting and glorious times. It is time for great expectations and also greater work. The United States of America is not going down! She is going up! For those “doom and gloom” prophets who prophesy against the United States and speak of its demise, they better not hold their breath, because it is not going to happen in this generation, not while you and I are still here!</description>
        <category>articles</category>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>What a Great Time to be Alive</title>
        
            <dc:creator>Cristina Sosso</dc:creator>
        
        <link>sogmi.org/articles/what-a-great-time-to-be-alive/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>sogmi.org/articles/what-a-great-time-to-be-alive/</guid>
        
            <media:content url="//images.contentful.com/vfgh62eq5a4k/4nw4mfMDOUUgUs4mOA08My/ac407c2b321fffd8b6052662550eb959/kristina-wagner-357533-unsplash__1_.jpg?w=800" medium="image/jpg"/>
        
        <description>I cannot put into words the awesome wonders of our Lord Jesus Christ! All I can say is that it is great to be alive (in Christ). Right before our eyes, we see the transformation of our nation and this is just the beginning! What’s even more exciting than this is the fact the Lord always shares His plans, His thoughts, and His heart with the Body of Christ if we have ears to hear and eyes to see!</description>
        <category>articles</category>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>A Word About the Transfer of Wealth</title>
        
            <dc:creator>Cristina Sosso</dc:creator>
        
        <link>sogmi.org/articles/a-word-about-the-transfer-of-wealth/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>sogmi.org/articles/a-word-about-the-transfer-of-wealth/</guid>
        
            <media:content url="//images.contentful.com/vfgh62eq5a4k/1Konxep5rK8Y6egiImGAcG/d2d2b495e23632ab6c7cb5044d81c794/freddie-collins-309833-unsplash__1_.jpg?w=800" medium="image/jpg"/>
        
        <description>In 1991, I was caught in a dream-like vision. In this encounter with God, He handed me a formula on how to find His kingdom. It was a series of very detailed instructions He expected me to follow. He told me that He would be sending laborers who would follow my lead, knowing fully well that they would find the kingdom. These people were matured and did not desire material things.</description>
        <category>articles</category>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Prophecy to the Church</title>
        
            <dc:creator>Coby Randal</dc:creator>
        
        <link>sogmi.org/articles/prophecy-to-the-church/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Nov 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>sogmi.org/articles/prophecy-to-the-church/</guid>
        
            <media:content url="//images.contentful.com/vfgh62eq5a4k/5KH3rRY5FuC4iaYoykeUEs/0c30b64b0c4a40c192d2fc121fc6153a/ben-white-292680-unsplash__1_.jpg?w=800" medium="image/jpg"/>
        
        <description>The following is a prophecy released back in 2010
We are entering a time when personal prophecy will become more and more rare. Continuing to hear the testimony of Jesus Christ, the prophetic mantle will address the Body increasingly on a corporate level instead of an individual level. Yes, remember the personal prophetic words that were released to you, but more important than that is the need for you to follow your prophetic instructions, concerning the Body of Christ and the Nations, to the letter.</description>
        <category>articles</category>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>I Am Restoring the Judges as in the Days of Old</title>
        
            <dc:creator>Cristina Sosso</dc:creator>
        
        <link>sogmi.org/articles/i-am-restoring-the-judges-as-in-the-days-of-old/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 22 Aug 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>sogmi.org/articles/i-am-restoring-the-judges-as-in-the-days-of-old/</guid>
        
            <media:content url="//images.contentful.com/vfgh62eq5a4k/6o5dw9ihQAcmM0C2mAkSu0/b1d6f13daa41c774c03045f97f7395aa/Sans_C3_B3n_matando_al_le_C3_B3n_-_Pedro_Pablo_Rubens.jpg?w=800" medium="image/jpg"/>
        
        <description>The following is a prophecy from August 22nd 2010.
Thus saith the Lord of hosts, “As I am restoring the judges as in the days of old, as I am a faithful God, not only for this nation, but for the nations of the Earth to bring forth the nations to the proper places of alignment and timing including the nation of Israel. This is your beckoning. This is your calling.</description>
        <category>articles</category>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>The Characteristics of a True Prophet</title>
        
            <dc:creator>Ed Grubb</dc:creator>
        
        <link>sogmi.org/articles/the-characteristics-of-a-true-prophet/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 21 Aug 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>sogmi.org/articles/the-characteristics-of-a-true-prophet/</guid>
        
            <media:content url="//images.contentful.com/vfgh62eq5a4k/34rFC5FS5a2Su4YQs0GW0K/bf8e90962701acda5f785ee00663cefd/bible.jpg?w=800" medium="image/jpg"/>
        
        <description>Real vs Counterfeit and Prophet Defined
A certain jewelry store sold man-made stones as though they were priceless, natural gems. This was happening for years and scores of men &amp;amp; women bought what they thought were precious stones. No one questioned the authenticity until someone with trained eyes pointed out they were man-made. How were people deceived? The counterfeit looked remarkably like the real. The difference was not noticeable unless you had a trained eye.</description>
        <category>articles</category>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Revival is Here</title>
        
            <dc:creator>Coby Randal</dc:creator>
        
        <link>sogmi.org/articles/revival-is-here/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>sogmi.org/articles/revival-is-here/</guid>
        
        <description>The fruits and signs that revival has come include:
True repentance brought on by the Holy Spirit; Jesus becomes not just Savior, but Lord over every area. Focus on the presence of God, knowing Him and His word. Falling in love with Jesus; not getting drunk on visions or gifts. A grateful heart of worship; God multiplies our faith by His word and faith works by love. We are delivered from the tree of the knowledge of good and evil, not striving about fear or emotions, but looking steadfastly upon Jesus, living by faith in Him that we may please God by Him in us.</description>
        <category>articles</category>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Prophecy From July 12, 2009</title>
        
            <dc:creator>Coby Randal</dc:creator>
        
        <link>sogmi.org/articles/prophecy-from-july-12-2009/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jul 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>sogmi.org/articles/prophecy-from-july-12-2009/</guid>
        
        <description>This is an excerpt of the July 12, 2009 prophecy given by the Lord through Pastor Cris.
The same thing that I did in the Philippines, with accreditation of signs and wonders in the realm of finances, saith the Lord, I will do now, if you are going to confer with Me, if you are going to put Me first, and if you are going to obey what you have learned and your instructions, saith the Lord, it will manifest starting this year.</description>
        <category>articles</category>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>